[
  {
    "question": "This is the first test question (yes).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "Yes",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the second test question (no).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "No",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the third test question (yes).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "Yes",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 3."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the fourth test question (no).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "No",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 4."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the fifth test question (yes).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "Yes",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 5."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the sixth test question (no).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "No",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 6."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the seventh test question (yes).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "Yes",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 7."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the eighth test question (no).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "No",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the ninth test question (yes).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "Yes",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the tenth test question (no).",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": "No",
    "explanation": "Due to explanation 10."
  }
]